bindaaslo.com 2014-06-28

# Privacy Policy Lowest Price in India at BindaasLo.com

At Bindaaslo.Com, we are extremely proud of our commitment to protect your privacy.We value the trust you place in us. Your privacy is very important to us. We do not publish, sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. The privacy practices of this statement apply to our services available under the domain and subdomains of www.Bindaaslo.com. By visiting wwww.Bindaaslo.Com you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our website.

**YOUR PRIVACY:-**

we are extremely proud of our commitment to protect your privacy. We value your trust in us. We will work hard to earn your confidence so that you can enthusiastically use our services and recommend us to friends and family. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Site.

Bindaaslo.com promises that we will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. From time to time we may reveal general statistical information about our Web site and visitors, such as number of visitors, number and type of goods and services purchased, etc. Your trust and confidence are our highest priority.

**COOKIES:-**

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a web server on a web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. We place both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive. The cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information.

**OPT-OUT:-**

There are times when we may collect personal information from you such as name, physical address or telephone number. It is our intent to inform you before we do that and to tell you what we intend to do with the information. Generally, you will have the option not to provide the information, and in the future you will be able to "opt out" of certain uses of the information. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit the Website, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers and services.

**SECURITY:-**

When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you put in before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information, we will employ reasonable security practices and procedures and current Internet security methods and technologies in compliance with Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules made there under.

**NOTE:-**

  * Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.
